we've just launched AI extensions and
我们刚刚启动了AI扩展名，
it's a whole new way to interact with the extensions in raycast it opens up
这是与Raycast中扩展的互动的全新方法
new possibilities enabling users to interact with these extensions in
新的可能性使用户能够与这些扩展相互作用
natural language using one or multiple extensions at once and today I want to
自然语言使用一个或多个扩展，今天我想
show you how they work so you can build or enhance an existing extension from
向您展示它们的工作方式，以便您可以从中构建或增强现有的扩展
our store so this video is aimed at developers but if you don't know how to
我们的商店，因此该视频针对开发人员，但是如果您不知道该怎么
code I would recommend that you stick around anyway because including AI
代码我建议您无论如何都会坚持下去，因为包括AI
extensions is really easy and I'm going to try and Vibe code with cursa and
扩展真的很容易，我将尝试使用Cursa和Cursa和
that's something I've never done before so let's see how that
那是我以前从未做过的事情，所以让我们看看如何
goes here we have a very basic extension that just renders some static data in a
去这里，我们有一个非常基本的扩展名，仅在一个中呈现一些静态数据
list this extension is not really useful but it's simple enough just to go over
列出此扩展名并不是真的有用，但仅仅是简单的
the basic concepts of an AI extension and that's going to help you understand
AI扩展的基本概念，这将帮助您理解
how to build your own so the first thing we want to do is
如何构建自己的第一件事是
create a new directory in the source and call it tools and in here we're going to
在源中创建一个新目录并将其称为工具，在这里我们将要解决
create a file called films. TS we're going to take the exact same data as
创建一个称为胶片的文件。 TS我们将采用与
before and we're just going to put it in here we create a const I like to call it
以前，我们只是要把它放在这里，我们创建一个const，我喜欢称呼它
tool where we just return the data and then we export default tool right once
我们刚刚返回数据然后我们正确导出默认工具的工具
we do this the next step is to go to packet Json so we can tell raycast that
我们这样做的下一步是去数据包JSON，以便我们可以告诉Raycast
there's this tool available as you can see here cursor is
有此工具可用，因为您可以在此处看到光标是
already being quite helpful and giving it a name this name needs to match your
已经很有帮助，并给它一个名字，这个名字需要匹配您的
file name a title and a description there's nothing else that we need to do
文件名称标题和描述，我们没有其他需要做的
and when I open up this extension in raycast we can see that now we have this
当我在Raycast中打开此扩展名时，我们可以看到现在我们有了这个
AI extension before we could go into this normal command and see a list of
在进入这个普通命令之前，AI扩展
the data but now we can go into this other command and I can get that same
数据，但现在我们可以进入另一个命令，我可以得到相同的
[Music]
[音乐]
data but in natural
数据但是很自然
language because this data is now available in AI you can start quering it
语言，因为此数据现已在AI中可用，您可以开始对其进行质疑
[Music]
[音乐]
or interacting with it just through natural language
或仅通过自然语言与之互动
so just to recap an AI extension is basically an extension that consists of
因此，仅仅回顾AI扩展，基本上是一个扩展程序，它由
one or more tools a tool is just a typescript file that returns a function
一个或多个工具工具只是返回函数的打字稿文件
that's going to eventually return some data call some API interact with your
最终将返回一些数据调用一些API与您的API相互作用
file system or whatever you want rcast then
文件系统或任何您想要的rcast然后
exposes this extension through this at menion UI that you've just seen and lets
通过您刚刚看到的Menion UI公开此扩展
users interact with it through natural language then it figures out which tool
用户通过自然语言与之互动，然后弄清楚哪种工具
to use and what to do but now we're going to do something a little bit more
使用和做什么，但是现在我们要做更多的事情
interesting and we're going to enhance a real extension from the
有趣的，我们将从中提高真正的扩展
store the extension that we're going to enhance is the resend extension which
存储我们将要增强的扩展名是重新启动扩展名
currently allows us to do a bunch of things such as looking at our domains as
目前允许我们做很多事情，例如查看我们的域名
well as all of our contacts it allows us to create new emails that you can send
以及我们所有的联系人，它允许我们创建可以发送的新电子邮件
directly through raycast and also create and manage your API
直接通过Raycast，还可以创建和管理您的API
Keys let's go ahead and create a new folder in source and we call it tools
钥匙让我们继续创建一个新的文件夹，我们称其为工具
just like we did before and the first tool that I want to create is the one
就像我们以前一样，我想创建的第一个工具是一个
that's going to allow me to send an email so we create a new file we call a
这将允许我发送电子邮件，因此我们创建了一个新文件，我们称
send. TS and we start by importing resend and setting it up with the new
发送。 TS，我们首先要导入并使用新的
resent providing the API key then you can see curs is already suggesting a
提供API键的RESENT，然后您可以看到Curs已经在暗示
bunch of stuff
一堆东​​西
here so here we just call resend. emails. send and we pass in these
在这里，我们只是打电话回去。电子邮件。发送，我们通过这些
parameters like before we're going to go to to packet Json and we're going to
像我们要去数据包JSON之前的参数，我们要去
tell raycast that there is a new tool available so now I can just open up rast
告诉Raycast有一个新工具，所以现在我可以打开Rast
mention resend and say send the email it's going to figure out which tool to
提及重新发送并说发送电子邮件将弄清楚哪种工具
use that Mak sense for the instructions that I gave so it calls the send email
使用该Mak的感觉进行我给出的说明，因此请致电发送电子邮件
tool and at the moment I'm just hardcoding all of these parameters so
工具，目前我只是对所有这些参数进行硬编码，所以
now just to check that this is working we can open up the browser and we can
现在只是为了检查这是否有效，我们可以打开浏览器，我们可以
see that the email has been received we going to exort con
看到已收到电子邮件，我们将迁出con
confirmation which is going to be an async function and this function is
确认将是一个异步函数，此功能是
going to return basically let's have a look at what cursor is suggesting yeah
基本上要返回，让我们看看光标的建议是的
it returns an object with info and info is an array of these name and value
它返回带有信息和信息的对象是这些名称和值的数组
Pairs and here is where you can show the user what you're about to do and the
对，这是您可以向用户展示您将要做的事情和
user can then confirm or reject let's put that in let's open up recast at
然后，用户可以确认或拒绝，让我们把它放在让我们打开重铸
resend and we just say send the email again and now what you'll see is that
重新发送，我们只是说再次发送电子邮件，现在您会看到的是
before sending the email we get this confirmation step we
在发送电子邮件之前，我们将获得此确认步骤
can confirm by pressing command enter or we can cancel by pressing scape keep in
可以通过按命令输入来确认，也可以通过按Scape保持来取消
mind not every tool needs this but if you're doing something that is
介意并非每个工具都需要这个，但是如果您要做的事情
destructive or something that can mutate some sensitive data you might want to
破坏性或可以突变一些您可能想要的敏感数据的东西
confirm
确认
first first thing we're going to do is we're going to define a type here we're
我们要做的第一件事是我们要在这里定义一种类型
going to call it input and we're going to put in here the
将其称为输入，我们将在这里放置
types of the parameters that we want to be dynamic in this case the two which is
在这种情况下，我们要动态的参数类型
an array of strings the subject and the content here we Define the input
一个字符串的主题和内容，我们定义输入
with the types and what you notice is that this function will then receive
随着类型以及您注意到的是，此功能将接收到
this input in the structure and in the shape that we've described and then we
在结构和我们描述的形状中的输入，然后我们
can just use this input to then populate the fields that we want okay so in this
可以只使用此输入来填充我们想要的字段，所以
case we're going to do that and also update over here
案例我们将要这样做，也可以在这里更新
like this so we do that for confirmation as well and for confirmation we type
这样，我们也这样做以确认并确认我们键入
this const as to. confirmation with your input this prompt no longer make sense
这个const。用您的输入确认此提示不再有意义
because it doesn't know who to send the email to right so here I would have to
因为它不知道该发送电子邮件给谁，所以我必须在这里
go send let's say Bruno he's going to be
去发送假设他要成为的布鲁诺
editing this video later so let's say Bruno at ray.com
稍后再编辑此视频，所以假设Bruno在Ray.com上
remember to take a break and now you may notice that the
记住休息一下，现在您可能会注意到
subject field is not here this little hard drive here
主题字段在这里没有这个小的硬盘驱动器
basically is the indicator that you have a local extension running and if you
基本上是您的局部扩展程序运行的指标，如果您
hover over this you can basically take a look at what input your function is
悬停在此方面，您基本上可以查看您的功能是什么输入
receiving so here we can see that it receives the content and receives the
接收到这里，我们可以看到它接收到内容并接收
two array but the subject line is empty here's how we can solve this inside your
两个数组，但主题行是空的，这是我们可以在您的内部解决这个问题的方法
type we can tell AI what type it expects for each key but what you can also do
类型我们可以告诉AI对每个键期望什么类型，但是您也可以做什么
here is start to provide some instructions for each of these values
这里开始为每个值提供一些说明
make sure it's based on the content of the email and now for the content um
确保它基于电子邮件的内容，现在用于内容UM
this is good don't include any introduction or salutation just the main
这很好，不要包括任何介绍或致敬
content so let's keep that there let's try again right all we did is we just
内容让我们继续说，让我们再试一次
gave AI some instructions internally we use this as well uh tell Bruno rc.com to
在内部给AI提供了一些指示，我们还将其使用uh告诉bruno rc.com
take a
拿
break this is good let's send it okay let's actually send this and maybe in
打破这个很好，让我们寄出好吧，让我们实际发送此信息，也许
the edit Bruno you can uh show us whether you received the email or not
您可以向我们展示您是否收到电子邮件，您可以向我们展示
[Music]
我希望你 [音乐]
I'm hoping that you
did thanks Pedro what I often like to do is quickly
谢谢佩德罗，我经常喜欢做的是很快
email myself with reminders of things what I want to be able to do is instead
向自己发送电子邮件，以提醒我想做的事情是
of being explicit I want to be able to do this in a more natural way and just
我希望能够以更自然的方式做到这一点
say hey just email myself right or just send me an email so how do we do that
说嘿，只是给我自己的电子邮件，或者只是给我发送电子邮件，所以我们该怎么做
when you open up an extension you can just go command K and
当您打开扩展名时，您只需命令k和
configure command as with any other command in raycast and in here you can
将命令与Raycast中的任何其他命令一起配置，在这里您可以
then provide some custom instructions now these are instructions that happen
然后提供一些自定义说明，这些是发生的说明
at the user level so now I can say um if I ask you to email myself use Pedro
在用户层面上，现在我可以说如果我要求您给自己发送电子邮件使用Pedro
rc.com I now should be able to go at resend remind me to buy
rc.com我现在应该能够重新提醒我购买
milk now it sends an email to Pedro rc.com with subject and the content this
牛奶现在将电子邮件发送给Pedro rc.com，并带有主题和内容
is a really important thing to know because depending on the extension that
这是一个非常重要的事情，因为取决于扩展
you're building it's really going to be powerful when users add their own
您正在构建用户添加自己的
instructions so as a developer you might want to include
说明，作为开发人员，您可能需要包括
this type of guidelines in the readme coming back to Bruno's example I could
这种类型的指导原则在我可以回到布鲁诺的示例中
also add another instruction there and say if I ask you to email Bruno then use
还要在那里添加另一项说明，并说我是否要求您给Bruno发送电子邮件，然后使用
this email address but as you can see this can start getting a little bit more
这个电子邮件地址，但是您可以看到，这可以开始获得更多
laborious to maintain and we're going to have some scalability issues to say the
努力维护，我们将有一些可扩展性问题要说
least here's what we can do resend has an API to create contacts
至少这是我们可以进行的，有一个API来创建联系人
so what I want to do is I want to create a contact list in resend and so when I
所以我想做的是我想在重新发送中创建一个联系人列表，所以当我
say hey email Bruno it's going to look it up in contact and it's going to find
说嘿，电子邮件bruno，它将在联系中查找它，并且会找到
his email address from there and just send him an email let's go ahead and
他的电子邮件地址从那里，只给他发送电子邮件，让我们继续前进，然后
[Music]
[音乐]
Implement a contact tool
实施联系工具
all right so now that we have these three tools we should be able to create
好吧，现在我们拥有这三个工具，我们应该能够创建
a contact so I'm going to say add Bruno to my contact
联系人，所以我要说在我的联系人
list so you see that first it calls the list audiences tool because it needs
列表，因此您首先要调用列表受众工具，因为它需要
that in order to call the create contact endpoint so if we follow this pipeline
为了调用创建联系人端点，因此，如果我们遵循此管道
here um to list an audience there are no input just an output where we get the ID
在这里列出受众，没有输入只有输出我们获得ID的输出
and for the next tool it then receives all of that as input in order to be able
对于下一个工具，然后将所有这些都作为输入接收，以便能够
to do it and because we have a confirmation step then we get this
为此，因为我们有一个确认步骤，然后我们得到了
little confirm button here to which we can just
这里几乎没有确认按钮，我们可以
confirm now it says Bruno has been added and now what we should be able to do is
现在确认它已经添加了布鲁诺，现在我们应该做的是
go list all my
去列出我所有的
contacts and then that caused the list contacts tool that's already pretty good
联系人，然后导致列表联系人工具已经很好
we've created three extra tools because they kind of depend on each other and we
我们创建了三个额外的工具，因为它们彼此依赖，我们
didn't have to even tell rcast which to depends on which to it's just able to
甚至不必告诉rcast，要取决于哪个
work it out all by itself all right so now that we have Bruno as a contact I
现在就可以解决所有问题，所以现在我们将Bruno作为联系
should be able to just go at resend tell Bruno to have a
应该只能重新恢复告诉Bruno有一个
break and take a day off next week okay then he lists the audiences
休息一下，下周休息一天，然后他列出了观众
list the contacts cuz it's trying to figure out who is Bruno it gets his
列出联系人，因为它试图弄清楚谁是布鲁诺
[Music]
[音乐]
details and then it wres writes up the email to which I'm just going to
详细信息，然后它写了我要去的电子邮件
send will you let me work to show you just one more thing we
[音乐] 发送给我让我工作，向您展示我们的另一件事
also have an internal extension for our hr2 code Bob and in Bob we can basically
也有我们的HR2代码BOB的内部扩展，在Bob中，我们基本上可以
uh interact with anything to do with HR so I can book time off I can check uh
UH与与人力资源有关的任何事情互动，所以我可以预订时间我可以检查
when Bruno is off on my team I can also um get some contact details of people in
当布鲁诺（Bruno）不在我的团队中时，我也可以从
the company so if I go to Bob and I ask how many people work at
公司所以如果我去鲍勃，我问有多少人在
raycast it's going to search all of the people and then it comes back to me with
Raycast将搜索所有人，然后再回到我身边
36 employees right now what I could do is I could say can you
现在有36名员工，我能做的是我可以说吗
add all the contacts who live in
添加所有生活的联系人
England to my recent
英格兰到我最近的
list now we're starting to use two different extensions together
列表现在我们开始一起使用两个不同的扩展名
right he got all of the contacts from Bob who live in England because it's a
是的，他从鲍勃那里得到了居住在英国的鲍勃的所有联系，因为这是一个
hr2 at the end of the day and it's now passing them through to resend to
HR2在一天结束时，现在正在将它们延续到
[Music]
[音乐] 确认，如果我问我，请显示我的
create all all of these contacts in recent so now I can
最近在最近创建所有这些联系人，所以现在我可以
confirm and if I ask resend show my
[音乐] 确认，如果我问我，请显示我的
contacts we should see that now we have Bruno plus three other contacts who live
联系人我们应该看到，现在我们有Bruno加上其他三个居住的联系人
in
在
England all right and now what I could do if I wanted to is I'm going to be
英格兰一切顺利，现在我想做的是我会做的
going to London next week for our hackathon so I could just send an
下周去伦敦参加我们的黑客马拉松，所以我可以发送
email to all of
电子邮件发送给所有
[Music]
[音乐]
them about us meeting up for dinner next
他们接下来我们会见晚餐
Friday so now it's going to send an email to all of these people with the
星期五，现在它将向所有这些人发送电子邮件
fact that I'm going to London next week and so let's go for dinner here is a
事实是我下周要去伦敦，所以让我们在这里吃晚饭是一个
pretty simple overview of what you can do with AI extensions how tools work how
非常简单的概述您可以使用AI扩展工具如何工作的AI扩展
you expose them through the pack of Json hopefully this gives you some ideas of
您希望通过JSON揭露它们
things that you can build I'm going to leave a link in the description for the
您可以构建的东西我将在描述中留下一个链接
documentation where it goes into a little bit more detail of a few extra
文档详细介绍了一些额外的详细信息
things that we haven't mentioned in this video but I just wanted to get this out
我们在此视频中尚未提到的事情，但我只是想解决这个问题
quickly shortly after the release so you can start building it and so thanks for
发行后不久，您可以开始构建它，所以谢谢
watching make sure to subscribe for more tips and news about raycast and maybe
观看确保订阅有关Raycast的更多提示和新闻
even more tutorials
更多的教程